[
    { "question": "", "answer": "" },
    {
        "question": "Oh my goodness, this lecture___it's never going to end.",
        "answer": "feels like"
    },
    {
        "question": "Did you check the weather outside? It___it's going to snow tonight.",
        "answer": "looks as if"
    },
    {
        "question": "Have you ever felt a cat's tongue? It___really rough.",
        "answer": "feels"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does stinky tofu smell like? It___vomit!",
        "answer": "smells like"
    },
    {
        "question": "That book___it's been used a lot because the pages are all dirty!",
        "answer": "feels like"
    },
    {
        "question": "She___she isn't very happy with you.",
        "answer": "looks like"
    },
    {
        "question": "Are you OK? You___you haven't been sleeping well.",
        "answer": "look as if"
    },
    {
        "question": "A lot of singers today___exactly the same.",
        "answer": "sound"
    },
    { "question": "Did you hear that? It___music.", "answer": "sounds like" },
    { "question": "Your boyfriend___a movie star!", "answer": "looks like" },
    {
        "question": "Tom___he hasn't taken a shower in three days.",
        "answer": "smells like"
    },
    {
        "question": "My skin___much softer since I started using SK-II.",
        "answer": "feels"
    },
    { "question": "You___you stepped in dog poop!", "answer": "smell like" },
    {
        "question": "You___you've been singing all night.",
        "answer": "sound like"
    },
    {
        "question": "This soup___terrible - itâ€™s really salty.",
        "answer": "tastes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Don't tell me any more. It___you're lying to me.",
        "answer": "sounds like"
    },
    { "question": "This milk___it has spoiled.", "answer": "smells like" },
    {
        "question": "Hitting your toe on a table leg___really bad for about one minute, and then it's OK.",
        "answer": "feels"
    }
]